Well, welcome back to
class. We'll go over the rheme with you.
We went with you
to Turn on the
Slavic word that we are somewhere in
the middle and we are talking about the
perfection of giving
and when we
reach the perfection of joyful diligence in Kyoto,
we will have done 14 years of work,
they will be
completed, and now they are talking about the types
of giving,
very
good, for example, you cannot offer
alcohol to someone who
suffers from alcoholism, such an
example, chuk here means
cow, an old word for sacrifice. It was such an
Indian tradition
to slaughter a cow and make an offering, wearing it,
and this type of giving, he says
that this is a
bad
idea, and there are many
stories of children who sacrificed a
cow and were born as a cow in the next life,
and then he has a whole list of
bad relationships
when with When
you try to do good things,
your mind should also be in a good
state, the right mood. When you
give money, for example,
like a road construction project,
then you should avoid certain
relationships.  mind and then giving
will be
strange you seem to give but at the same
time in such a state a little
grumpy the second
means there is a little more than that
country for example I'll
spit on
them Let our amount be a little
more this is called a competitive
attitude
Yes everyone will know that I gave more than
everyone else everyone
pay attention RTI in Sanskrit famous I think I
hope that everyone will hear what a
cool dude I am that gives so much
money a little depressed You should
be bright state good mood
You should be happy when you give You
should not think like that
when they have already finished this money
beg for as much as
possible Therefore, donation is
also a teaching m
means a very important word and
means sunam said that sunam when
her speech she
inspired everyone so much all the countries also began to
touch me I got excited so
excited And now I have to now
I have to give he says I got so
excited and gave a lot was
impressed yes this happens when
you are in this business of giving
sometimes you get very carried away and promise a
lot they say I will build  retreat cabin
and then later What was I even thinking about why do
I need this so it's very important not to
regret just shut up and give and
talk don't give this time don't
think about it just shut up Give and
enjoy it And next time just
keep yourself within limits control yourself
well
means I will help friends but I will not
help other
people this is also a
relationship prejudice that you
only help those whom you like And who
you don't like you don't help For
example, in my country My country every
10 years it chooses a new enemy whom
it will
hate When you are 71 You also
pay attention to this Pay attention and enemies change
all the time periodically and here in this
wound terrible di live in this
mustache I wish it weren't no Those are already normal But these hi
they are enemies in our country This year
they are enemies And next year there will be
some other
enemy every year something new every
5 years a new enemy that's why every time people
in my country they say Arabs are
bad Germans are bad Russians are
bad  other people are bad every time
I hear things like that I try to
go to this country on the contrary
I went to
Morocco and spent two years in a village there a
two-month retreat I studied the
Quran with a local imam they were from the
Taliban they are big enemies of the United
States we were good friends They are all
wonderful people and we had a great
time I learned Arabic and forgot it right there
is such a joke in the monastery I forgot
what What have you ever learned
everyone learned every two years enemies
change so don't believe it
forget about it everything they tell you
just try to make friends with everyone everyone is the
same Everyone wants to be friends with you
so be friends with people it's so
great to say that I am friends with everyone in the
world and I like any country people ask
me
when I lived in New York and when I
visited these Muslim
countries they asked me I am from Manhattan I say what is
Manhattan I say it's there an
island outside the
United States because in  That time
they bombed Arab
countries, all great guys, you need to get
used to it. When you travel a lot
and you find that people are all the same,
they are all sweet, just talk to them.
Be
friends
means: Let your giving not be
dirty, Let it not be stained with
these
prejudices. The next
picture. I think sneakers should
be, yes, when I heard about this, people
buy
sneakers and then they try to make them
perfect, perfectly
snow-white all the time. Why buy white
sneakers? It seems like such
madness. They buy white sneakers and then
try to jump with special sprays
so that they are
snow-white. I don't even have time to
put on shoes. They also spray some kind of special spray on them. It's an
interesting idea. And how he
concludes the section on the perfection of giving.
Concluding this section, this is a very beautiful
section and you can make a whole teaching in
Diamond
M. He
quotes Shay, a very famous book by
Shanti Deva, which few people know about.
He wrote two great books. One of them
is called Shay, we know the guide to
life, and he wrote another one. It
means that he
collected all the cool tips from the most ancient
su. I  I always wanted to teach this
because the manual is
some kind of secret Secret hit rock
role and I worked with this book and I realized
why there is a reason why it is not so
famous it is a little bit like well
sad boring I don't want to talk about it like that
of course but it was
not he who wrote it he just collected
different quotes from different
sources and it is not like his other
book because his book And this is one of the
greatest books ko wrote this
guide to the lifestyle of bass error
sacha it is just such a collection of different
quotes from different sources and that is why I
decided not to work with it for some time
Ino quotes it here and says
listen there is something you should
know about day and it is very
beautiful he says that all the things
you own
all your possessions all your
things your
time as soon as you become
yours All you have already sold it all is already
sold out understand your
body your white
sneakers your house your
money
VM
what you own for Like bachy you already promised
to give it and
now it no longer
belongs to you you just take care of it
until you
complete  This process of giving
everything you own you have already dedicated to
other people and your time and your body
you have already offered it you have
already agreed to
become every living being therefore you
no longer
own it you just take care of it
temporarily store it until
you complete the delivery as if it were from the
zone all these things that are stored in the
warehouse until they are
sent So your body your money
your time as soon as you took the vows of
bahi sava you have already made a
promise to give everything to other people you
just take care of these things until a
certain time when people
ask so and now having delivered all this to me
now I want your money now I want
your house now I want your time
and shantideva
says while all these things are still in the
warehouse you have a responsibility
to take good care of it it no longer
belongs to you as soon as you have accepted lunch and
signed all your money all the things
that belong to you all your time and
your
body have already been given they have just not been delivered
to the address yet so you cannot
treat your body badly until you
have delivered this
product it no longer belongs to you it
belongs  other people, so you
have to stay healthy, you have to,
it's your direct responsibility
because it's not your body anymore, and I
think this is a very, very beautiful idea,
it's like you say,
Shena. When you
give it to me, my wife says that I have a
belly button,
but she sees my belly button because my
shirt is opening up and I don't fit in it anymore.
Guys like to
open it up like this and show their breasts. And my
shirt opens up here, in this
place, and my wife says, you can see me like this,
so you can't gain weight
because you'll start getting sick. You can't
gain weight. You have to
take care of your body. You have to go
to the gym. You have to do yoga. You
have to eat wisely because this body
doesn't belong to you. It's not your body, you're
just a temporary Guardian of
this body. You take care of it. Here in
this warehouse until you
send it away. And I think this is a
very, very beautiful argument and
statement. And this is how he
ends the first perfection. He
quotes Shanti de, he says, you have no
right to overeat and gain weight, and you
have no right not to sleep.  You have no
right not to take care of your body
because you already
promised it to others with this body. You promised to give it away.
What does it mean that you should
join the Good
Night Club? You have a
slide. If you want to
irritate
our people, ask about things that
they don't know about. It
seems to me that this idea of ​​the Good
Night Club is one of the best ideas. You
promised. I do it here from 1:00 a.m. to 5:00 a.m. and at home from 1:00 a.m. he
comes to me until I
wake up and walk around like this. I'll think, Well,
where's my computer, where's my
phone,
and I need to, I need to look. What's the
temperature in
Irkutsk? And then I think, well, maybe,
what difference does it make? It doesn't
matter. When you become a member of
this book
club, you
sometimes think about what strange
information we sometimes give us. Well, strange
information we sometimes look for on the
Internet. True,
I looked for this information and it's
called the Good Night Club. At
10 p.m., you get rid of all your
gadgets. I give away when my wife is at home.
I put the phone, for example, on her
side of the bed so that I don't have to
roll over and
stretch if her  No, then I give it to Rob and
Rob takes all my
gadgets
there is a joke and then you get this
paper book and these are
translations and Leave one rdo table at
10B Open the book from I swear to you
in 2 minutes you will simply turn off you
will fall asleep
vorna and my favorite is Mamika in 2
minutes I fall asleep so buy this
book put it next to your with your
bed put your computer
your phone so far away that you can't
get there otherwise if you are in a hotel
for example
add the TV remote there
I don't have a TV at home But when I
travel in a hotel there are also bullets
so please become members of this
club Good night These are the best
things I have taught I have
2.5 million files on my computer and I have
been teaching all my life This is the
coolest thing you will sleep well You
will be happy You have you you will be
creative you will not do nonsense
at night and I really haven't slept for 8
hours in a long time and now I sleep Like a child and
10 o'clock in the morning I just pass out at 6
o'clock I wake up
I can work I start
somewhere 5 minutes to work and until 11 I
don't meet anyone I work 5 hours and
this is wonderful it's great
if you came here so that I can teach you
and this is the best What can I
teach you So join this
club What is our short name Good
night And also just a night
club probably in your place when you
sleep Ben will play something from Jimmy
Hendrix this is a cool gift that
I give you so don't wait until until
6 o'clock do it now and you will be
much more productive and
your mind will be clearer and happier
and your meditation will be incredible
read a book before you fall asleep And
when you wake up
meditate for 510 minutes and your minutes Your
whole life will change Your life will change
if you came here to learn something
Here is your KB Good
night So advice
on how to take care
of it from other
parts parts and  three groups total 12 So let's
go
First you already promised to give your body to
other people you made a promise If you
accepted
You said somewhere that I am a servant
This is lunch I promise to be a servant I
give my body so this is no longer
your body do not take do not take vows for
pleasure this is a huge
commitment then all your things
are sent to warehouses
made a
commitment that all your things
belong to
others and here is the important
part until you until the time comes to
send it all this is
your
responsibility take care of your
body do not harm your body do not
give it away do not do
yoga do
physical exercises you already promised this body to someone
else so you must
take care of it I don't know about you I have
problems taking care of
myself these are some because of some
selfish reasons I'm not very good at this
when my wife tells me
take care of yourself you need to eat general
says my wife you need to eat more
vegetables otherwise you will just
harm yourself I'm like Okay
And I do a lot of things that
harm me but how when she tells me
Listen, you're
damaging other people's property right now, it
doesn't belong to you anymore, I'm like, yeah, that's bad, it's
not mine anymore, like I
borrowed something from someone, like
someone's car, and smashed it up, yeah,
Stanley, by the way, no, he didn't. It was him, this
happened to him, the car is still
somewhere in Rush, it's been 2 months already,
we don't want to damage
other people's things, and so Ken means things
that harm your body, too
much sugar, too much coffee,
not enough
sleep, too
busy. When you're very, very busy,
that's not very
good. It means protect your body, it's
your
responsibility to take good
care of your body, because you, you, you
have to live a long, long life.
Yes, it took a million years for you to be in this
room, so take care of this
person, it's a very, very valuable thing. I don't
know. It doesn't matter. What do you think? You're
priceless. You're one in 10 million. If you
think you're a normal person, you're not
normal, you're here in this room, and it
took you a million years of hard
work to get here, and don't waste it.
hurt
yourself take
responsibility sleep well
eat right don't
overwork
ok sometimes play listen to pop star they
say taco game yes I play
role you should you should sing
pleasure pleasure
how do you
support yourself say that there is no time for boredom
and you are
here bte
and I say I need to have
fun I can't date
should have
fun too that means
cleanliness is a reason to
deceive other people and what does it
mean to continue to care for
white white
sneakers you already gave away these sneakers
so if they got dirty
take care of it if you
harm it if you do
something to harm it better
take care of yourself when you get to
my
age you have to go to doctors
I don't like it never I have never had
doctors never did that but when
you live to a certain age you
have to forget yourself you have to find
good right doctors and
go to these
appointments for
check up because you have to try to
live as long as possible
be ready to give it take care of
it and don't pollute not pack let
it stay clean let your heart
be clean let your body be
healthy  for the next person who
will use
it and then he talks
about the fact that you should get to know
your body in the future, you also have this and
this is the responsibility to take care of your
body in the future life, the next life, I
la I can’t take care of myself in this life
And now you want me to
worry about the body in which I have
not yet been born and the answer is yes, you
already have a responsibility in the future, your future
body has also already been
sold, it is in the
Amazon VKO, so you have a
responsibility to accumulate karma that will make sure that
in the next
life you have a good one because
it has also been
sold, not only should you take care
of your body in which you were born
because it no longer belongs to you,
your future bodies, you have also already made
promises, they have also already been sold, they just were
not delivered to their destination, so
you have a
responsibility to accumulate this karma in order to
create a good healthy body in the future
life Cool I think this is such a
cool game I’ll think about it Well, okay, okay,
I’ll try to be
generous because I have already promised my body
in the next life and
I want you to  I was before that there was
enough money I will take care of
those who are hungry I will take care of those who are
homeless on the streets because I want
my body to be cool in the future
because I already promised it It's
like you promised to give something to your
grandson I will give you a cool gift for
your birthday next year and
then you should already start collecting
money he says
Be
ready to give protect your body and
let it be in good shape and
also your body in the future and
then he mentions eight
things that you must
prepare for That is, eight qualities of
your future body that you must
prepare
now You must
give great to
know that you can with to get these
Seme so that you
have a good
body in the rest of your life By the way, it's cool to think like that I think
it's fun and amusing It's not selfish at all that
is, you should take care
of your body You must make sure
that you will have a good body in the future you must
take care of your body in the future
because you will give it away and you can't
give away some bad faithful
thing  You should give away good
quality things. If you
tell me about it this way, then I will be
inspired.
And the writer says, "Go look for
Shan." He knew that we would have a
library of Asian classics
to find. I found them in our
database, and here you have eight of them. Lore,
first, protect lives. Help sick
people in this life so that your body will
live a long life in the future. And so, first,
accumulate
reasons for
your future body. When
you have a new car and it already has high
mileage, you don't want such a car to be
bought and it breaks down. You
wanted a car with low
mileage. Therefore, accumulate, accumulate these
reasons. Yes, cars with good mileage,
help people who are sick.
Second, be
patient, don't get angry. It's
clear. And you are like, what should you do with your
body? With a body for your future life, we want
to be attractive. This is not at all
selfish.
This is
considered very
practical. If you look good, then
many people will
come to your classes. You must look
good. And Asha said, "I'm so glad
I was born a handsome man."  cute
because everyone comes to my
classes Yes, that's true, he said so, this is
karma that you must prepare
for your future body, this means don't
be angry, don't be angry in this life
You really pissed me off, but I won't
send you to the next life, think like this
You are how you are how you
drive I won't be angry with you I already
promised this body in the next life,
so I won't be angry with you so
that I look good and
attractive
Be
generous so that in your next life you
are born in a country that has enough
money and this will only
help you if you are If you give birth in a
poor country, you will not have sources,
you will not have resources to help
other people I'm not saying that you are a bad
person, you are a great person, but
It's like Here is a man who built
roads for us and he also built a
student center, that's it
Cool, you need roads, yes So you
need a new car, a new road I went and
bought a car, you have a new car
Okay, give you a new car, a new
tractor, I'll buy you a new
truck I remember when he came,
Shan and I were collecting money, I think
200,000 dollars, and it was like this  big
deal he said okay I'll do it
and we used all this money and he
says Here
you still got it in my opinion
200 times five That's why it
turned out so beautiful Be generous Be generous
with  Build so that in your future
body you live in a country where there is money so that you don't
live in a poor country. I'm not saying that
you are a bad person,
but that I should quit Rita's job
earning money. No, I'm not talking about that.
Give it away. How can you? Pain is this?
You can. If you have 10 dollars and you
give it away, you will get the same
result as this guy who
built a student center. What
can you give away without harming
your family, without harming
yourself? Let you have a nice
house, a nice car, proper food, and
give away as much as you can, and that's great.
Chucheva
means share power. Share your strength.
Whatever power you have, share
this power with other people. For example,
if
you or
you, and so on, share a
position, share it. Be
generous with your power. Let other
people
also use it, and therefore share
the responsibilities and duties if they
want. Give them the opportunity to do
cool things too. Give them a chance to be
bosses. If you are a boss, the
best way to be a boss is to simply
let
others share these
boss responsibilities, and then you will be a boss.
Share time.
Give, share your power, share the
position you hold, don't be
greedy, and then in your next life
you will have the same
power, you will
lead.
Fifth, keep your
promises. When you said something,
try to keep it.
Keep your promises. Don't
forget about them. It seems to me that
keeping a promise means remembering that
you promised 50%, so when you
make a
promise, try to mentally write it down.
This is what I promised. Therefore, I need to
do this. Try to
mentally record it or write it down in your phone
and then keep your word. It means
keeping your promises. Don't make promises
too easily. Don't make promises. It's easy, but
since you've already made a promise, please
keep it no matter what happens, and then in the
next life, and then in the next
life, people will believe you, people will
listen to you. It's so
great to accumulate karma so that people will
say, "Give." It
took me a long time to accumulate some
karma, it took me a long time to
accumulate karma, but I must say that
it's very
cool, people said so, I must
do it.  I'm like, yes, hold back,
hold your
words,
sixth, try to have a good reputation in your
next life,
this
means taking care not to
blah-blah about other people's problems, about
other people's failures, don't waste your
time talking about other people, to
criticize, to judge other people,
don't waste time, everyone has
problems, we all have problems, we
all have bad habits,
each of us
if someone in this world
pretends that he doesn't have a bad
habit, it seems to me that they just
pretend that they don't have a bad
habit because
then you wouldn't be in this world.
If you didn't have a bad habit, otherwise you would
n't be here, someone tells me this. I'm
as clean as a whistle
already here on this earth. If you're
here, this is
where all the bad guys are, then
this
world is where we are. We all have
problems and bad habits, so don't
waste your
time creating
lists of consciousness in your mind, creating
bad habits, writing down
other people's habits, you don't need to. You have
enough work here. It's better to work on
your bad habits. And when you
work it out.  You help them so that
in the future you have a cool body and
so that you
have power and so that you are
famous. You can use this.
And you can use it for good and for
bad. You can depend on it.
You can harm yourself. If you
want to be famous. But if you are
famous, you can use it. You
know, ethos.
This will help
many.
Seventh, in each
country there are different
levels. Each country has different
social levels and there are countries
where in the world the
strong-willed ear is stronger
than the right one. You belong to the upper class. The
upper caste. Oh, look how
beautiful she is. Her left ear is twice as big
as her right
ear. This is the world. Such
worlds exist. We also
have strange things, for example, his nose, I don't
know, short or, on the contrary, too
long. He must be a good person,
something like that, to be
born in the future. So that you have a
big ear, left or right, or
whatever will be popular on that planet,
so you must be prepared. I
have a
vision of myself. I came up with it and I'm waiting. I thought of what
I will look like in advance.
I know what kind of person I
will be. I've already thought of everything.
You must be the kind of person who
will be respected in  society, here about the World Cup I'm
trying and societies are
different in some societies If you
talk a lot, you are respected in others,
on the contrary, you say nothing, you are
respected, so it doesn't
matter in each country its own traditions and foundations,
but Try to accumulate karma so that you are
born in the best in the
next life.
About Tai, he is wonderful, he is so cool, his
left ear is so
huge. Try to create
karma. This may sound stupid, but
nevertheless. And the
last thing. Create such karma. In order for
you to have a very healthy body, we say that
it has veins, a
lot of energy, a lot of liveliness, so that
it is
healthy. You can live a long
unhealthy life, live a long time, but an
unhealthy life, therefore, is not long enough.
We also need a body that would be
absolutely healthy, which
you can put pressure on. You
can get up early. You can build
temples. You can build
stupas and then study something else. 8 o'clock,
you get
100 dollars and everyone immediately
woke up.
What nickname is there to
create
karma for these ko, these, these
in short, raise your hands
joyfully, diligence, no, in short, than you can.
combine
these So here's the man with the microphone He
decides
good No well let's burn
if three bad answers there will be four steps
so one more try and I cancel
the deal
abdication of the Supreme Court
forget the picture Show the last picture
watch your white
sneakers Don't forget Don't forget
remember the picture we had take care
of your body in this
life take care of your body in the
next life watch that Be this this
person
who
will clean for others every morning You must take care of
your body in which you were born and you
must take care of the body in which
you don't have yet
it's your
responsibility I don't know something has become more
difficult to live yes
ela I like it I think I have
problems taking care of myself but if
you say that I have to take care of
myself for the sake of other people then I
react to a big corporation in
Nyor Omsk is
on fire from the ring you need to work a lot You
can't go home slame do
Rome You have to stay here I'm like this I'm leaving
And he's like this I'll fire you I'm like this
everything is fine I won't
miss classes he disappeared so Poli
from here and six months later he  go ma
they always call
you
somewhere to one minute they tell you
come here to the
office Mac you are the one and only
Without you we are nothing and
nobody we can do nothing without you what we
do You must help us Please We have a
big shipment tomorrow please please
you are the best I am like yes I
understand If you tell me that this is for
someone then I will react I am like
yes I can I will eat vegetables if it is for
one of my students for my
future students I will eat these vegetables
if it is for me for my sake I am not
interested in this yesterday we had a very tasty
latus from a group in Mexico and someone
tried to
add spinach to it My
cat
She eats wet food so
wet and dry food she is like this
I ate all the yummy and
gave away the spinach But if you say for the sake of others you
need to eat spinach Well okay I will eat it
so be it and it seems to me that we are all like this
if it is for someone else then
we can
do it So He told about the body when
I need to stop Anya
is there 10 say thank you  to someone or
what Or I will
say
when that is, we have 5 more minutes
right this is important yes because then we
go to the next perfection Let's
finish with the first He says everything the same
applies to what to own So the
first is the case of your body you must
take care of your body
because of your future body also for the sake of others
But now you need to take care of
all your things for example about your
car this is interesting by the way You must
take care of your car because
it is no longer yours you
borrowed it when you drive in your
car you are already driving in a car that you
gave to other people They just have
n't received it yet They haven't taken it yet and
it's no longer your car so you must take care
of your things I don't like taking care
of things at all I really don't like taking
care I just hate
that the car needs to be
taken somewhere to a garage to get it fixed and
checked But if you then
turn this on that's what you are so special
Mike we
can't do without you
someone must take care of the car
because it should be
able  maybe you will have to
take another person in this car
to the hospital, so you have this
responsibility to take good care of
your things because you will need
them in order to serve others, of
course, you must look after your house by the way,
your house will be clean of
all the junk, because when you
die, someone will have to, take
out all this junk, it's so annoying, a
friend dies and you go home, come on,
Lord, here all week you have to
clean everything, so let your house be
clean, don't collect a bunch of junk, let
your house be clean, let your life
be
easy, just imagine that you are going to die
tomorrow and don't let other people
choose, it
seems to me that I just take all the
junk, take it out and
throw it in the
trash, and then I go out on the street and start
digging through this trash again, half of it is
needed, my wife says, Lord, you are already
happy,
don't let someone else
do this for you later, when you are, you don't know
when you are, so clean up
now, let it be like the
very steps, be prepared to give up everything
you
own  try
what you own because someone
might need it next
week there's a joke yes your
clothes will go looking for a new owner
when you
die in
America you give away there's a special
store where you stand so
take care of your
things
means means that let your
news that you do
n't keep do not keep things in the house
that were stolen or were obtained
dishonestly everything should be clean
because you can't then give it to other
people all the things that were obtained
dishonestly this is an interesting idea Don't
deceive other people to get
other things Because when you die
and all these things are already offered to other
people They will be back do
not
pass on do not pass on dirty
things to others all the things that belong to Vlad they
must be clean Of course you must
get them in clean ways sweet
ways everything that everything you own
should not be
theft kamm w
in your home we
must teach That's Mari con Mari
con purity of karma everything should be
karmically clean by the way we too  You need to
offer to do such a program
together with
her and don't forget to
also accumulate cool things for your
future life,
but your motivation should be that
in the next life I will have very
cool things that I can give to
others. Finally, I will have a Tesla in my
future life and then I will give it to
someone, that is, something cool to
give to
others. And
the last thing,
and then we will have 9000
thanks, says
VS, what you own. And now he says
do the
same, do the same steps with
your good seeds, and it's interesting, really
very interesting. You
should. Every time you meditate, at
the end of meditation, practice
when we give away, give away good Semina,
remember how we did meditation today,
you can give away your good hay. Is it possible to
pretend I'll give away the seeds?
Yes, we can, we can teach other people to
give away their good seeds, and
then he
says, Don't
control $100. Who
said two answers, there is
one answer here. When I, when I put Yes, I
said that I would give $100 and gave And
sometimes I just don't put the answer
so good that I  I offer 100
dollars
So what does Anger have to do with what does
Anger have to do with this for 100
dollars What is the connection between anger and
this about this ses we are talking with this te
sha all the good
seeds and therefore there will be no
good seeds to dedicate them to the next
life shi good seeds also do not
belong to you anymore oh my God this is
generally very serious Okay I'll poison
my car already good
Sava you already promised to give everything you have
including your good seeds your
good seeds in your mind they
no longer belong to you they
belong to other people You have a
moral responsibility morality
not to harm your good seeds
to your good seeds and the
best way how you destroy all your
good seeds is Anger so you
should avoid anger Because
you will destroy these seeds their seeds
that no longer belong to you it's as
if you borrowed a car and crashed
it they no longer belong to you you
have no right to be
angry because you have no right to
destroy all the good seeds in your
mind because you have already
given them away Wow This is complicated
I'm almost done and he  The
last one says it's also your
moral responsibility not only
to protect the good seeds that you have
but also to strengthen and increase them and it's your
duty. If
you have money that you have already
promised to someone but haven't delivered, then it's your
responsibility to invest this money
and earn money on it and to give even
more.
For example,
I want to collect money, 10,000 dollars
for a
Latin American
tour. We
met in the toilet with friends and
talked and decided that I should give
this money today,
but I want to
earn more interest on it because I want to
give maybe more than 10 but 11,
so it's
your responsibility to give
more than you promised. You must
earn interest on your seeds and
now for 100 dollars and I'm
just already
silent. This is the last thing we need to do.
How will you create these
percentages of your lethal seeds? 100%
raise your hands and say this
orange box.
By the way, next time you
arrive, be those children,
agree to receive 50% of the winnings, but
So, by
the way, I'll give 200 dollars to cleanse
my body, everything is like this.  So now
I have mental
seeds, good mental seeds, I have
ini for everything I have, I've already
dedicated them to others, I just kept them for
some time, and I can earn
interest on them instead of giving away
$10,000, for example, on a tour, I can
give away $11,000 if I invest them wisely,
how to invest wisely
to turn them into 100 good metal
seeds, 110 good lethal seeds the easy
way,
coffee,
meditation, and as I also said, rejoice,
I also said rejoice,
yes, $100, both here and
there, give more seeds, deliver, because the
money is a business at
10%. You took $100,000,
and you must give back $10,000, give back another $20,000 on top,
and then you will be very
popular. They will constantly lend
you money. Let's always give more and
do the same with your mental
seeds.